<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on</title><link>/docs/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deals</title><link>/docs/projects/deals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:30:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>/docs/projects/deals/</guid><description>1 Overview Deals, available in both purchasing and selling transactions, enable users to add or remove free items linked to existing items in the Item table. Selling and purchasing deals are conveniently managed within the Item profile itself.
Item deals are automatically applied based on the quantity of each item within a transaction.
Note: All current deals are set to recursive by default at the moment. 2 Maintenance 2.1 Child DocTypes Deals are maintained in the Item profile and are separated by two types of deals.</description></item><item><title>Discounts</title><link>/docs/projects/discounts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:30:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>/docs/projects/discounts/</guid><description>1 Overview Discounts are a crucial feature in purchasing and sales transactions. It enables the users to configure item rates more flexibly according to multiple factors. Discounts are maintained and are associated with the following master data DocTypes:
Item Supplier Customer Item discounts are discounts applied to the Price List Rate of each item in a transaction. Supplier, Customer, and Principal discounts are discounts applied to the whole transaction, distributed among the items' Rates.</description></item><item><title>Reports Configurations</title><link>/docs/projects/reports-configurations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 11:10:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>/docs/projects/reports-configurations/</guid><description>Reports Configurations Overview The &amp;ldquo;Reports Configurations&amp;rdquo; feature has been introduced to empower clients to tailor their report consumption experience according to their unique business needs. Reports, crucial tools for decision-making, may not always require the same data or presentation. A flexible solution is provided, allowing each client to customize report filters and columns to align with their preferences.
Traditionally, Script Reports were designed with a one-size-fits-all approach. However, differing client requirements must be addressed.</description></item></channel></rss>